Hello everyone.
Guess where we're going?
Nicaragua!
Guys, we're gonna take you along with us on this journey.
We're about to get surfy.
We're gonna surf and it's gonna be awesome.
So, let's freaking go.
Go, we gotta take the up, take a plane, take shuttle, take another plane, and then shuttle there, but
we're gonna be there at 2 a.m. tonight, so it's gonna be awesome.
So I'm excited, let's go.
We're walking to the up, gonna take the train to the airport.
Yes,
so
the vlog be in my vlog.
We're in El Salvador at our stopover.
We're doing a vlog of the trip.
Rowan, if you want to be in it.
Hey!
So we're doing our stopover, and now we're in a little art museum.
Gorgeous.
All right, we're on our last, I don't even think you'll be able to hear us because it's so loud.
And the music.
They're playing freaking Coca Melon.
But we're on the flight to Nicaragua now.
It's only one hour, Managua.
So awesome.
And only then after a two and a half hour, three hour car ride, and then we there.
We in stage two.
Yes.
Here we are.
Nice.
Now only a 2.5 hour drive.
On February 15th, we woke up in San Juan del Sur, Nicaragua.
It was warm and a perfect escape from the cold of Toronto.
We're currently in, finally in the stage three, was not good today.
We are okay.
You guys coming back, but we're gonna go surfing.
What a lovely first day.
It was genuinely so nice to escape the cold, I cannot say that enough.
We got to go surfing for like two hours, had a great lunch, and we honestly stayed at the beach for like four hours, which was very nice
and restful after a long travel day, and we stayed and watched the most beautiful sunset.
Okay, we're at the beach today.
Yes, guys.
You stay tuned.
Now, what was awesome about where we were staying, which was Dream Sea Surf Camp, San Juan del Sur, was that they actually planned a bunch of activities
for everyone, and this was one of them.
So they drove us all to this rooftop bar.
It was so beautiful.
There was some live music.
It was just calm.
The drinks were good.
The food was great.
And it was just a lovely place to spend the evening.
Thank you.
Music
show where we're going.
We're going, we're going, not there.
Up there.
Nice.
It begins.
Almost to the top!
To the top, yes, but it's not a limit.
Do
it,
yes,
yes, I'm so f-ing nervous.
Okay, we're currently back at the hostel, and we gonna do a beach picnic in an hour, so that should be really fun, but right now I just
taking a nap, but surfing was good today.
I feel like every day I getting more waves, so that was nice.
This is the last full day here.
Today we just woke up and had a relatively chill morning.
And at 1, I think we're going to go surfing.
But it's been really nice and relaxing right now.
I'm just working on an assignment because I have an essay worth 35% of my grade due on Monday.
Just trying to finish that.
We're going surfing later, so I have a couple hours to work on this.
This was genuinely such a lovely trip.
I've done a lot of solo trips, but doing this with two of my really good friends was honestly such a joy and a gift and a
pleasure, and I'm so grateful that I was able to do this with them.
We also connected with so many new people, which was awesome.
We got to see so many beautiful things, and I will definitely be back in Nicaragua at some point.
You.